Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 52, folder: 2 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Steamship Lines and Agencies Serving the Port of New York, Publication (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Steamship Services via The Port of New York, Publication (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Guide to Air Shipping via the Port of New York, Publication (Box 52, Folder 2)
    Fall 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Guide to Air Shipping via the Port of New York, Publication (Box 52, Folder 2)
    May 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Administration of a Port Authority, Publication (Box 52, Folder 2)
    By Austin J. Tobin. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Port of New York: Crossroads of the World's Ship and Air Lanes, Publication (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Traveler's Guide to Port Authority Facilities, Publication (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Box: 52, folder: 3 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Dateline: 2000 AD, Publication (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Box: 52, folder: 4 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Employee Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Box: 52, folder: 5 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Potomac Sand and Gravel Co. Agreement, Publication (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Box: 52, folder: 6 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: "Dear Mom", Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Box: 52, folder: 7 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Equal Employment Opportunity Policy, Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Box: 52, folder: 8 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Pratt & Whitney Aircraft, Publication (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Box: 52, folder: 9 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Welcome: Precision's New Fayetville, NY Plant, Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Welcome to Precision, Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Box: 52, folder: 10 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: News Caster, Publication (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Box: 52, folder: 11 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Successful Personnel Relations: A Challenge and Opportunity for American Business Leaders, Publication (Box 52, Folder 11)
    By Richard P. Ettinger. May 19, 1952. Item is in English.
- Box: 52, folder: 12 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Tie-In, Publication (Box 52, Folder 12)
    Autumn 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Tie-In: forst Issue 1963, Publication (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: The Tie-In, Publication (Box 52, Folder 12)
    Summer 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Tie-In 40th Anniversary, Publication (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Box: 52, folder: 13 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Princeton Panel: A Center for the Study and Teachin gof the Principles of American Capitalism, Publication (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Box: 52, folder: 14 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Princeton Panel: A Center for the Study and Teaching of the Principles of American Capitalism, Publication (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Box: 52, folder: 15 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Industrial Relations Section: Department of Economics and Social Institutions, Publication (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Industrial Relations Section Department of Economics: Orientation, Organization and Programs, Publication (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: A Report of Activities 1926-1955, Publication (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Industrial Relations Section Department of Economics: Orientation, Organization and Programs, Publication (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Industrial Relations Section Department of Economics: Orientation, Organization and Programs, Publication (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Box: 52, folder: 16 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Section Department of Economics: Orientation, Organization and Programs, Publication (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Box: 52, folder: 17 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1960-61, Publication (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: A Report of Activities: 1926-1955, Publication (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: A Report of Activities: 1926-1955, Publication (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: The Industrial Relations Section in 1957: A Report to the President of Princeton University, Publication (Box 52, Folder 17)
- Box: 52, folder: 18 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The First Fifty Years, Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
- Box: 52, folder: 19 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Printing Industry of America, Publication (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Could You Use a $300,000-a-year Assistant?, Publication (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Printing: Self-Marketing Revolution, Publication (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: What MPS Means to You: Handbook of Services of Master Printers Section for Open Shop Printing Concerns, Publication (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: What Can PIA Do For Me?, Publication (Box 52, Folder 19)
- Box: 52, folder: 20 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Facts and Figures About America's Printing Industry, Publication (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Basic Services of Union Empoyers Section of PIA, Publication (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Basic Information about PIA, Publication (Box 52, Folder 20)
- Box: 52, folder: 21 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Bread 'n Butter: A Better Living for All Through Mutual Understanding, Publication (Box 52, Folder 21)
    Vol 5 No 1. Item is in English.
- Box: 52, folder: 22 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Printing Specialtiies & Paper Products Joint Emplyer & Union Health & Welfare Fund: Agreement and Declaration of Trust, Publication (Box 52, Folder 22)
    October 24, 1952. Item is in English.
- Box: 52, folder: 23 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, Publication (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Moonbeams: Manufacturing Edition, Publication (Box 52, Folder 23)
    June 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Moonbeams: Manufacturing Edition, Publication (Box 52, Folder 23)
    August 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Moonbeams: Manufacturing Edition, Publication (Box 52, Folder 23)
    July 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Moonbeams: Manufacturing Edition, Publication (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Item 6: Moonbeams: General Office, Publication (Box 52, Folder 23)
    July-August 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Moonbeams Salutes Baltimore Plant's 25th Anniversary, Publication (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Item 8: Moonbeams: Manufacturing Edition, Publication (Box 52, Folder 23)
    March 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Annual Report, Publication (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Item 10: Moonbeams, Publication (Box 52, Folder 23)
    August 1964. Item is in English.
- Box: 52, folder: 24 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Agreement, Publication (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Management's Responsibility toward Stabilized Employment, Publication (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 52, Folder 24)
    May 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Hourly Contract, Publication (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: Contract, Publication (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Item 6: Working Agreement between Ivorydale and St. Bernard Employees' Representation Association and The Proctor and Gamble Company, Publication (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Item 7: Agreement between the Proctor and Gamble Independent Union of Port Ivory, NY and the Proctor and Gamble Manufacturing Company, Publication (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Item 8: Index, Publication (Box 52, Folder 24)
- Box: 52, folder: 25 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Management Considerations of a Consumer Oriented Business, Publication (Box 52, Folder 25)
    By Dean P. Fite. Item is in English.
- Box: 52, folder: 26 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The Proctor & Gamble Profit Sharing Trust Plan, Publication (Box 52, Folder 26)
    July 1, 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Proctor & Gamble Disability Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 52, Folder 26)
    January 1, 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Proctor & Gamble Profit Sharing Dividend Plan, Publication (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: The Proctor & Gamble Stock Purchase Plan, Publication (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: The Proctor & Gamble Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Item 6: The Proctor & Gamble Survivor Income Insurance, Publication (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Item 7: Prudential Surgical Medical Expense Insurance, Publication (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Item 8: Group Dental Allowance Insurance, Publication (Box 52, Folder 26)
    January 1, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Prudential Major Medical Expense Insurance, Publication (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Item 10: The Proctor & Gamble Cmpany Annual Report, Publication (Box 52, Folder 26)
- Box: 52, folder: 27 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Simulation: Its Use in Employee Selection and Training, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Proctor and Gamble Helps You Plan Your Future, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: You and P&G, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: Communicationsa way of working with people within a company, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 5: My Pay at P&G, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 6: Proctor & Gamble Summer Preview of Industry, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 7: Proctor & Gamble Manufacturing Opportunities for Business, Science and Economics Graduates, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 8: Summer Workshop at Proctor and Gamble, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 9: Data Processing Proctor & Gamble, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 10: What Kind of Research does Proctor & Gamble Do?, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 11: Proctor & Gamble Management Opportunities: Development, Engineering, Manufacturing, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 12: Proctor & Gamble Career Opportunities in Overseas Division, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 13: Proctor & Gamble: Engineers, Chemists, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 14: Proctor & Gamble: Careers in Business Management, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 15: Future for Engineers and Chemists, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 16: P&G and I, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 17: The Moon and Stars, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 18: Revised Guarantee of Regular Employment to Proctor & Gamble Employees, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 19: First Year in Industry, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
    By James B. Dougher, EE. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Opportunities for Electrtical Engineers, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 21: Company Information Sheet for Proctor & Gamble, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 22: Proctor & Gamble & You, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 23: Opportunities for Women in Proctor & Gamble's General Offices, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 24: International Careers in Business Management for Foreign Students Proctor & Gamble, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 25: Field Office Administrative Management Proctor & Gamble, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 26: Market Research Managemtn Proctor & Gamble, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 27: Financial and Accounting Management Proctor & Gamble, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 28: Advertising-Brand Management Proctor & Gamble, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 29: Hiring today for the years to come, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 30: Proctor & Gamble and Urban Problems, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 31: Proctor & Gamble and Urban Problems, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 32: Proctor & Gamble and Urban Problems, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 33: Proctor & Gamble Twelve Doors to a Rewarding Career, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 34: Job Description - Freezer Ivory Foreman, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
- Box: 52, folder: 28 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Developing Leadership in America Through Education, Publication (Box 52, Folder 28)
    By Neil McElroy. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Story of Soap, Publication (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: The Development of Management From Within, Publication (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: In P&G's summer trainingStudents Become the Plant 'Managers', Publication (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Item 5: Proctor & Gamble is People, Publication (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Item 6: P&G Beliefs About Management Training, Publication (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Item 7: information from Proctor & Gamble, Publication (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Item 8: One Businessman to Another, Publication (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Item 9: 75, Publication (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Item 10: The Moon and Stars, Publication (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Item 11: The Moon and Stars, Publication (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Item 12: The Moon and Stars, Publication (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Item 13: Proctor & Gamble Tells Its Story, Publication (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Item 14: Detergents Continuously, Publication (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Item 15: Merrill Lynch Stock Appraisal on Proctor & Gamble Co., Publication (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Item 16: Doorway to the Future, Publication (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Item 17: The Corporate Director, Publication (Box 52, Folder 28)
- Box: 53, folder: 1 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Business Week, Publication (Box 53, Folder 1)
    Nov. 4, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Summer Training in Industry, Publication (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Photodrawing & Modeling at Proctor & Gamble, Publication (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Matrix Description, Publication (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Matrix Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Summer Preview of Industry, Publication (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: How Our Business System Operates, Publication (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Box: 53, folder: 2 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: President's Address to the 48th Annual Meeting and First Biennial Convention, Publication (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: The Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada, Publication (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Box: 53, folder: 3 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A Report on the Activities of the Profit Sharing Research Foundation, Publication (Box 53, Folder 3)
    By J.J. Jehring. April 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Progress Report on the Profit Sharing Research Foundation, Publication (Box 53, Folder 3)
    1951-1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Director's Annual Report, Publication (Box 53, Folder 3)
    July 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Projects to be Undertaken by the Profit Sharing Research Foundation, Publication (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Box: 53, folder: 4 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: What Every Businessman Should Know About Profit Sharing, Publication (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: New Research in Profit Sharing, Publication (Box 53, Folder 4)
    By J.J. Jehring. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A Progress Report on the Profit Sharing Research Foundation, Publication (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Profit Sharing on eof the New Breed of total systems incentives, Publication (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Box: 53, folder: 5 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Prudential Family, Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Prudential's Economic Forecast, Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The Prudential mortgage loan mirror, Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: The Prudential Record, Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
    October 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Prudential Bulletin, Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
    November 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Field Management Digest, Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
    March 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Pru News, Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
    Vol 2, No 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Management Digest, Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: The Prudential Southwestern Pulse, Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: The PrudentialLog, Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
    February 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Prudential Southwestern Frontier, Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: the prudential 85th annual report, Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Management Digest, Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Box: 53, folder: 6 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Prudential's Economic Forecast, Publication (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: The Prudential Story, Publication (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: The Return to Feudalism, Publication (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Box: 53, folder: 7 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Settling Grievances, Publication (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Box: 53, folder: 8 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Any Ideas?, Publication (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Box: 53, folder: 9 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: New Career Horizons: The Prudential Insurance Company of America, Publication (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Job Opportunities at the Prudential for 1955 High School Graduates, Publication (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Current Opportunities for Male College Graduates, Publication (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Opportunity and Security with the Prudential, Publication (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Selection Guide-Posts, Publication (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: my name is jean, Publication (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Do you want to be an actuary?, Publication (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: PB Employment Forms, Publication (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Box: 53, folder: 10 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Psychological Corporation 30th Annual Report, Publication (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Industrial Division, Publication (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Box: 53, folder: 11 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Annual Financial Report, Publication (Box 53, Folder 11)
    September 30, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Annual Financial Report, Publication (Box 53, Folder 11)
    September 30, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Annual Financial Report, Publication (Box 53, Folder 11)
    September 30, 1963. Item is in English.
- Box: 53, folder: 12 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Explore America's Challenging Problems with the Public Affairs Institute, Publication (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Part 7 of Hearings before the House Select Committee on Lobbying Activities, Publication (Box 53, Folder 12)
    July 14, 1950. Item is in English.
- Box: 53, folder: 13 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Labor in America, Publication (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Box: 53, folder: 14 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Letter to Member, Publication (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Long Range Goals of the Public Personnel Association, Publication (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Box: 53, folder: 15 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Personnel News, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
    Vol 37 No 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Personnel News, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
    Vol 37 No 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Personnel News, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
    Vol 37 No 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
    October 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
    December 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 12: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 13: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
    March 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
    January 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 16: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 17: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 18: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
    September 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 20: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
    August 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 22: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 23: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 24: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 25: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 26: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 27: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
    June 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
    July 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 30: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 31: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 32: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 33: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 34: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 35: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 36: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 37: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 38: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 39: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
    March 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 41: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 42: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 43: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 44: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
    April 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 46: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 47: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
    Januray 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 48: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 49: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 50: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 51: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 52: The Personnel Man, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 53: Public Personnel Association Annual Report for the year 1967, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 54: Letter to all members, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 55: Letter to member, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 56: Letter to member, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 57: WANTED: A Qualified Test Technician for the PPA Staff!, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Item 58: Personnel Relations News, Publication (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Box: 53, folder: 16 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Association Public Relations, Publication (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Box: 53, folder: 17 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Public Relations Society of America, Inc. By-Laws, Publication (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Box: 53, folder: 18 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Timely Items of Interest, Publication (Box 53, Folder 18)
    July 26, 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Timely Items of Interest, Publication (Box 53, Folder 18)
    June 14, 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Timely Items of Interest, Publication (Box 53, Folder 18)
    June 1, 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Timely Items of Interest, Publication (Box 53, Folder 18)
    July 12, 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Timely Items of Interest, Publication (Box 53, Folder 18)
    June 28, 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Timely Items of Interest, Publication (Box 53, Folder 18)
    November 1, 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Timely Items of Interest, Publication (Box 53, Folder 18)
    October 18, 1971. Item is in English.